Contact

jemarko@sbcglobal.net

www.linkedin.com/in/jenna-marko-1abab838 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Healthcare
Quality Patient Care

Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Jenna Marko

Case Management Nurse at Blue Shield of California Los Angeles, California

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Currently working as a traveler open to new opportunities in nursing. Skilled in Customer Service, Patient Advocacy, Patient Education, Critical Thinking, and Telemetry. Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Registered Nursing/Clinical Nurse Leadership from Rush University.

Experience

Blue Shield of California Case Management Nurse February 2020 - Present (5 months)

Interim HealthCare Inc.
Home Infusion RN
October 2019 - Present (9 months)
Los Angeles, CA, United States

Kaiser Permanente Travel Registered Nurse December 2018 - September 2019 (10 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

AMN Healthcare
Travel Registered Nurse
August 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 2 months)

Stanford Health Care Travel RN April 2018 - October 2018 (7 months) Float Pool RN

Kaiser Permanente

Travel RN

January 2018 - April 2018 (4 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Med-Surg/Tele

St. Luke's The Woodlands Hospital

Travel RN

September 2017 - December 2017 (4 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Med-Surg/Tele/Women's Health

Holy Rosary Healthcare

Travel RN

May 2017 - August 2017 (4 months)

Banner - University Medical Center

Registered Nurse

October 2015 - May 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Phoenix, Arizona

RN/Team Leader in the Outpatient Observation Unit

Presence Health

Staff Registered Nurse

January 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 9 months)

Saints Mary and Elizabeth Medical Center, Saint Mary Campus

Telemetry RN

US Department of Health and Human Services

Caregiver

February 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 6 months)

Right At Home

Caregiver

August 2011 - November 2011 (4 months)

Chicago, IL

Education

Rush University

MSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2013)

Northern Illinois University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Rehabilitation Services · (2007 - 2011)